<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Return returnVersion="2022v4.0" xmlns="http://www.irs.gov/efile" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ReturnHeader binaryAttachmentCnt="0">
    <ReturnTs>2023-03-03T14:48:35-07:00</ReturnTs>
    <TaxPeriodEndDt>2022-12-31</TaxPeriodEndDt>
    <ReturnTypeCd>990EZ</ReturnTypeCd>
    <TaxPeriodBeginDt>2022-01-01</TaxPeriodBeginDt>
    <Filer>
      <EIN>391661544</EIN>
      <BusinessName>
        <BusinessNameLine1Txt>SHAWANO COUNTY ECONOMIC PROGRESS INC</BusinessNameLine1Txt>
      </BusinessName>
      <BusinessNameControlTxt>SHAW</BusinessNameControlTxt>
      <PhoneNum>7155265839</PhoneNum>
      <USAddress>
        <AddressLine1Txt>1263 S Main Street</AddressLine1Txt>
        <CityNm>Shawano</CityNm>
        <StateAbbreviationCd>WI</StateAbbreviationCd>
        <ZIPCd>54166</ZIPCd>
      </USAddress>
    </Filer>
    <BusinessOfficerGrp>
      <PersonNm>Paul Kersten</PersonNm>
      <PersonTitleTxt>SCEPI Board President</PersonTitleTxt>
      <PhoneNum>7155265839</PhoneNum>
      <SignatureDt>2023-03-09</SignatureDt>
    </BusinessOfficerGrp>
    <IRSResponsiblePrtyInfoCurrInd>1</IRSResponsiblePrtyInfoCurrInd>
    <AdditionalFilerInformation>
      <TrustedCustomerGrp>
        <TrustedCustomerCd>1</TrustedCustomerCd>
        <OOBSecurityVerificationCd>11</OOBSecurityVerificationCd>
        <LastSubmissionRqrOOBCd>1</LastSubmissionRqrOOBCd>
        <AuthenticationAssuranceLevelCd>AAL2</AuthenticationAssuranceLevelCd>
      </TrustedCustomerGrp>
    </AdditionalFilerInformation>
    <TaxYr>2022</TaxYr>
    <BuildTS>2023-04-26 12:10:37Z</BuildTS>
  </ReturnHeader>
  <ReturnData documentCnt="4">
    <IRS990EZ documentId="R000001" referenceDocumentId="R000004" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <MethodOfAccountingCashInd>X</MethodOfAccountingCashInd>
      <WebsiteAddressTxt>www.shawanoecondev.org</WebsiteAddressTxt>
      <Organization501c3Ind referenceDocumentId="R000002">X</Organization501c3Ind>
      <TypeOfOrganizationCorpInd>X</TypeOfOrganizationCorpInd>
      <GrossReceiptsAmt>165355</GrossReceiptsAmt>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartIInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartIInd>
      <ContributionsGiftsGrantsEtcAmt>165000</ContributionsGiftsGrantsEtcAmt>
      <ProgramServiceRevenueAmt>209</ProgramServiceRevenueAmt>
      <MembershipDuesAmt>0</MembershipDuesAmt>
      <InvestmentIncomeAmt>146</InvestmentIncomeAmt>
      <SaleOfAssetsGrossAmt>0</SaleOfAssetsGrossAmt>
      <CostOrOtherBasisExpenseSaleAmt>0</CostOrOtherBasisExpenseSaleAmt>
      <GainOrLossFromSaleOfAssetsAmt>0</GainOrLossFromSaleOfAssetsAmt>
      <GamingGrossIncomeAmt>0</GamingGrossIncomeAmt>
      <FundraisingGrossIncomeAmt fndrsngEventContriPrevRptAmt="0">0</FundraisingGrossIncomeAmt>
      <SpecialEventsDirectExpensesAmt>0</SpecialEventsDirectExpensesAmt>
      <SpecialEventsNetIncomeLossAmt>0</SpecialEventsNetIncomeLossAmt>
      <GrossSalesOfInventoryAmt>0</GrossSalesOfInventoryAmt>
      <CostOfGoodsSoldAmt>0</CostOfGoodsSoldAmt>
      <GrossProfitLossSlsOfInvntryAmt>0</GrossProfitLossSlsOfInvntryAmt>
      <OtherRevenueTotalAmt>0</OtherRevenueTotalAmt>
      <TotalRevenueAmt>165355</TotalRevenueAmt>
      <GrantsAndSimilarAmountsPaidAmt>0</GrantsAndSimilarAmountsPaidAmt>
      <BenefitsPaidToOrForMembersAmt>0</BenefitsPaidToOrForMembersAmt>
      <SalariesOtherCompEmplBnftAmt>144036</SalariesOtherCompEmplBnftAmt>
      <FeesAndOtherPymtToIndCntrctAmt>1166</FeesAndOtherPymtToIndCntrctAmt>
      <OccupancyRentUtltsAndMaintAmt>8917</OccupancyRentUtltsAndMaintAmt>
      <PrintingPublicationsPostageAmt>483</PrintingPublicationsPostageAmt>
      <OtherExpensesTotalAmt>8235</OtherExpensesTotalAmt>
      <TotalExpensesAmt>162837</TotalExpensesAmt>
      <ExcessOrDeficitForYearAmt>2518</ExcessOrDeficitForYearAmt>
      <NetAssetsOrFundBalancesBOYAmt>167074</NetAssetsOrFundBalancesBOYAmt>
      <OtherChangesInNetAssetsAmt>-71040</OtherChangesInNetAssetsAmt>
      <NetAssetsOrFundBalancesEOYAmt>98552</NetAssetsOrFundBalancesEOYAmt>
      <CashSavingsAndInvestmentsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>167074</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>98552</EOYAmt>
      </CashSavingsAndInvestmentsGrp>
      <LandAndBuildingsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>0</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>0</EOYAmt>
      </LandAndBuildingsGrp>
      <OtherAssetsTotalDetail>
        <BOYAmt>0</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>0</EOYAmt>
      </OtherAssetsTotalDetail>
      <Form990TotalAssetsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>167074</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>98552</EOYAmt>
      </Form990TotalAssetsGrp>
      <SumOfTotalLiabilitiesGrp>
        <BOYAmt>0</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>0</EOYAmt>
      </SumOfTotalLiabilitiesGrp>
      <NetAssetsOrFundBalancesGrp>
        <BOYAmt>167074</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>98552</EOYAmt>
      </NetAssetsOrFundBalancesGrp>
      <PrimaryExemptPurposeTxt>Promote economic development in Shawano County, Wisconsin</PrimaryExemptPurposeTxt>
      <ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
        <DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT: Put together an RFP for the vacant Reinhart facility. Worked with potential operators to take over operations for Owens Flooring. Continued outreach to the real estate and development community. Met with eight contractors. There is some interest in new businesses in the business park and there are frequent calls on available space in our downtowns, especially Shawano. Worked on financing packages for a couple of potential businesses in the Shawano area. Pfefferle has signed a tenant to the Owens Flooring property on a five-year renewable lease. Attended WADC in Wittenberg as they are working on workforce housing and day care issues. They seem to lose young families due to those two reasons. Met with WATCO. They operate the Fox Valley and Lake Superior Rail Road. The company purchased the CN rail assets between Shawano and Appleton. Novolex has reached out to SCEPI regarding the extension of a rail spur between their two facilities. In addition, Charter Manufacturing is a large rail user at their Saukville facility and have a long relationship with WATCO. SCEPI has facilitated meetings between WATCO and both Novolex and Charter. SCEPI also worked with Novolex on identifying a rail consultant and SCEPI was able to connect Novolex's consultants in Atlanta to VIA Rail in Maribel, WI. VIA Rail has a long history of designing rail projects in Wisconsin and a strong track record in obtaining grants. Met with representatives with Kerber Rose to discuss the Main Street Bounce Back Grant and the potential to host a seminar in the fall on how to transition your business, either to a new owner or the next generation. We have had several Shawano County business owners retire and the business just closed. A Texas based Site Locator who is working with a local business on a project expansion in Shawano County. Worked with NEWREP to disseminate a wage benefit study for Northeast Wisconsin. Results will be aggregated region wide and also broken down to the county level. Worked with a warehouse developer interest in constructing a 100,000 square foot warehouse if we can identify 50,000 square feet of users. NEWREP Wage and Benefit study was completed. Met with the Village of Pulaski to discuss additional development, especially the need for more hotel rooms. Worked with the Maple Lane broker, SVN to show potential buyers the facility. Completed two preliminary site location requests. Continued developer/investor outreach. Providing one on one business consulting as community members are looking to start or formalize a business idea. Working with two hemp-based building supply businesses to both develop their business plan and generate equity investments into their projects. The expansion of TimberPro in Shawano will add manufacturing space and a training center for new and existing employees. Assisted the City of Shawano with loan agreements as multiple properties are in the process of being acquired or renovated. Completed two New North requests for available sites and buildings. Participated in a NEWREP Benefit Study (Kerber Rose is doing the study) hoping to gauge the level of benefits companies are providing to their employees. Bounceback letters continue. We are in the process of working through a couple that were initially rejected but should be funded. They are becoming a bit more burdensome due to some significant fraud activities in the state. Working with a number of entrepreneurs needing space in the county. Main Street Shawano is a prime request for retail-based businesses. We receive around 2-3 of these requests each week. Harvest Moon met with Wittenberg for a building site and discussions on potential financing. Company has 300 acres of industrial hemp under contract for next fall and needs a facility to process the hemp. Small warehouse users looking for heated space Benjamin Marlow started his business BMar Capital in Bonduel. Many years of experience in finance recently based in the Cayman Islands https://www.bmarcapital.com/about/. A couple of restauranteurs looking at vacant businesses and potential funding options. SVN continues to market the Maple Lane facility and have responded to requests related to demographics and local market conditions. Maple Lane has a number of issues with potential investors. The primary issue is the cost to retrofit all the rooms to include a full bath in each one. Completed a New North request for available sites and buildings. Continued developer/investor outreach. Worked with a number of entrepreneurs needing space in the county. SVN continues to market the Maple Lane facility and responded to requests related to demographics and local market conditions. Completed New North requests for available sites and buildings. Met with Marion Body Works to discuss their needs in the county. Labor continues to be an issue. Continued work with TimberPro on their expansion.</DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>
        <GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>0</GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>
        <ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>68880</ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      </ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
      <ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
        <DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>HOUSING: Met with Northshore Health Care on the progress at their Maple Lane facility. Whispering Pines has some interest from developer on the conversion of the lodge into possibly a lifestyle community. Recovery housing continues to move forward. Initial findings of the Housing Study indicate that we do not have enough market rate housing in the community. Solid demand for single family development, over 55 housing and market rate/higher end multi-family development. Met with Jay Hintze Executive Director with SVN. MSA has completed the final draft of the housing study and we expect the full report by the end of the month. The key take away in the study is the need/demand for market rate housing. Met with developers interested in projects in both Shawano and Bonduel. Recovery housing continues to move forward. Met with the Wittenberg Village Board on a potential multi-family project. Met with several contractors who have multi-family investors. Worked with a local business to upgrade apartment units on the south end of Main Street. Recovery housing continues to move forward and they are working with a couple of different operators that would provide the technical support for the project. Met with a housing development in Cecil looking to add more single level complexes to the existing development. Attended NEWCAPs strategic planning meeting and a discussion regarding the development of housing in Shawano County. Continued participation in the recovery housing work. Facilitated a meeting between the Village of Cecil and a housing developer. Toured NEWCAP's apartment complex in Marinette. Met with Swiderski on the housing proposed project in Wittenberg. TIF changes have been completed and the acreage is available for development. Gresham spec build is framed and enclosed with occupancy planned for some time this spring. Stockbridge-Munsee Community has RFPs out for duplexes and they are in process for the same on multi-family. Continued builder/developer outreach promoting the completed housing study and the need for market rate housing in the county. Further discussions on Multi-family in Cecil, type, potential expansion, etc. Continued participation in the recovery housing work. Fundraising is moving along with nearly $85,000 committed. Met with Abby Bank and encouraged them to bring some of their single family developers to the market and take a look at doing subdivision development in Shawano.</DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>
        <GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>0</GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>
        <ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>38267</ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      </ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
      <ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
        <DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>BROADBAND: Design Nine will provide an overview of the Broadband project at the NEWREP meeting. MSA has scheduled a meeting with local government leaders to discuss next steps in Broadband development. Nsight is working with the Town of Richmond to expand broadband through the township. AT&amp;T/Bug Tussel is opening offices in Shawano County and will begin to deploy more fiber in the community Cirrinity (Wittenberg Telephone) is expanding the broadband support throughout the SMC and will continue further buildouts of their network in that region. Bertram is now on the next phase of connecting those without line of sight to a wired solution. Starlink has been deployed in the region with success. Design Nine provided a detailed study of Shawano County with recommendations to the focus group. Cirrinity has a strategy to fully deploy broadband throughout the western half of Shawano County. AT&amp;T/Bug Tussel have sited three additional wireless broadband/cell towers in the county and should have that coverage on-line by this fall. Nsight has applied for a PSC grant in the Town of Richmond to expand their fiber network. The middle mile project conversation creating a fiber ring in Shawano County continue. The New North Broadband study has been completed with representatives of the 18 counties meeting on 6/22 to discuss next steps. The full broad band study for Shawano County is posted on the SCEPI website. Presented at the New North/Competitive Wisconsin event on Broadband regarding reasoning for broadband mapping in NE Wisconsin. Continued work on developing a fiber ring and closely monitoring PSC grant application cycle. Broadband - "Internet for All" Event October 25th with overviews on future funding and state initiatives in Wausau. Matt Hietpas from the County was attending. Executive Committee has had initial proposals (very preliminary) from Bug Tussel and Cirrinity on potential fiber ring in the county. This ring would connect county buildings and serve as a backbone to extend fiber to residential users in the county.</DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>
        <GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>0</GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>
        <ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>30613</ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      </ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
      <ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
        <DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>COVID-19 and Miscellaneous: Bounceback awards have been funded in Shawano County. We currently have 5 applications waiting for final approval and two additional are in the application process. Active on conference calls with the Delta/Omnicron variant and the changes we are seeing in our health care community. Still awaiting additional disbursements of ARPA funding from the state. WEDC announced that the Main Street Bounce Back Grant Program will be extended until the end of 2022. Meetings: CHAT, US Chamber, PACE, NEWREP, Chamber seminars, CESA, WEDA, WEDC, RDA, Youth Apprenticeship, NWTC. Attended the Governor's Conference on Economic Development. One of the identified needs to assist on the workforce shortage is childcare. Attending the Shawano School District focus group on school facilities. Commissioned a Capstone project with the UW-Oshkosh Economics Department to measure the economic impact Shawano Lake has on the local economy. Interestingly enough we recently received a request for that information. Released the links to the NEWREP Benefits Study to the community. Attended the New North annual meeting. Attended the Insight networking event. Attended the Shawano School District listening sessions. Presented SCEPI's annual update to the County Board. Worked with The Chamber, NWTC and Community Education to develop networking event. Worked with the Chamber, NWTC and Community Education to develop networking event around issues impacting the business community. October 26th, 2022 will be the first event. Kerber Rose will present the results of the Northeast Wisconsin Benefits Survey which will allow employers a chance to benchmark their wage and fringe packages against other employers. Attended Manufacturing First workshop. Active in New North updates. Continue to Chair NEWREP-recent guest was Jayne McQuillan. She spoke on best practices in transitioning business ownership. How many businesses are not prepared and as a result forfeit incredible amounts of money.</DescriptionProgramSrvcAccomTxt>
        <GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>0</GrantsAndAllocationsAmt>
        <ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>15307</ProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      </ProgramSrvcAccomplishmentGrp>
      <TotalProgramServiceExpensesAmt>153067</TotalProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Peter J Thillman</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Chief Economic Development Officer</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>50</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>104722</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Bruce Milavitz</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Executive Committee</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>1.00</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>James Davel</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Executive Committee</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Eddie Sheppard</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Joe Miller</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Joe Dawidziak</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Steve Gueths</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Eric Voight</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Jim Hauer</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Member</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>0.25</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Paul Kersten</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board President</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>1.00</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Mary Wetzel</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Vice-President</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>1.00</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
        <PersonNm>Tracy Kersten</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>SCEPI Board Secretary/Treasurer</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>1.00</AverageHrsPerWkDevotedToPosRt>
        <CompensationAmt>0</CompensationAmt>
        <EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>0</EmployeeBenefitProgramAmt>
        <ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>0</ExpenseAccountOtherAllwncAmt>
      </OfficerDirectorTrusteeEmplGrp>
      <ActivitiesNotPreviouslyRptInd>0</ActivitiesNotPreviouslyRptInd>
      <ChgMadeToOrgnzngDocNotRptInd>0</ChgMadeToOrgnzngDocNotRptInd>
      <OrganizationHadUBIInd>0</OrganizationHadUBIInd>
      <SubjectToProxyTaxInd>0</SubjectToProxyTaxInd>
      <OrganizationDissolvedEtcInd>0</OrganizationDissolvedEtcInd>
      <DirectIndirectPltclExpendAmt>0</DirectIndirectPltclExpendAmt>
      <Form1120PolFiledInd>0</Form1120PolFiledInd>
      <MadeLoansToFromOfficersInd>0</MadeLoansToFromOfficersInd>
      <TaxImposedUnderIRC4911Amt>0</TaxImposedUnderIRC4911Amt>
      <TaxImposedUnderIRC4912Amt>0</TaxImposedUnderIRC4912Amt>
      <TaxImposedUnderIRC4955Amt>0</TaxImposedUnderIRC4955Amt>
      <EngagedInExcessBenefitTransInd>0</EngagedInExcessBenefitTransInd>
      <TaxImposedOnOrganizationMgrAmt>0</TaxImposedOnOrganizationMgrAmt>
      <TaxReimbursedByOrganizationAmt>0</TaxReimbursedByOrganizationAmt>
      <ProhibitedTaxShelterTransInd>0</ProhibitedTaxShelterTransInd>
      <StatesWhereCopyOfReturnIsFldCd>WI</StatesWhereCopyOfReturnIsFldCd>
      <BooksInCareOfDetail>
        <PersonNm>Peter Thillman</PersonNm>
        <USAddress>
          <AddressLine1Txt>1263 S Main Street</AddressLine1Txt>
          <CityNm>Shawano</CityNm>
          <StateAbbreviationCd>WI</StateAbbreviationCd>
          <ZIPCd>54166</ZIPCd>
        </USAddress>
        <PhoneNum>7155265839</PhoneNum>
      </BooksInCareOfDetail>
      <ForeignFinancialAccountInd>0</ForeignFinancialAccountInd>
      <ForeignOfficeInd>0</ForeignOfficeInd>
      <DonorAdvisedFndsInd>0</DonorAdvisedFndsInd>
      <OperateHospitalInd>0</OperateHospitalInd>
      <TanningServicesProvidedInd>0</TanningServicesProvidedInd>
      <RelatedOrganizationCtrlEntInd>0</RelatedOrganizationCtrlEntInd>
      <TransactionWithControlEntInd>0</TransactionWithControlEntInd>
      <PoliticalCampaignActyInd>0</PoliticalCampaignActyInd>
      <LobbyingActivitiesInd>0</LobbyingActivitiesInd>
      <SchoolOperatingInd>0</SchoolOperatingInd>
      <TrnsfrExmptNonChrtblRltdOrgInd>0</TrnsfrExmptNonChrtblRltdOrgInd>
      <PartVIOfCompOfHghstPdEmplTxt>NONE</PartVIOfCompOfHghstPdEmplTxt>
      <PartVIHghstPdCntrctProfSrvcTxt>NONE</PartVIHghstPdCntrctProfSrvcTxt>
      <FiledScheduleAInd>1</FiledScheduleAInd>
    </IRS990EZ>
    <IRS990ScheduleA documentId="R000002" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <PubliclySupportedOrg509a2Ind>X</PubliclySupportedOrg509a2Ind>
      <GiftsGrantsContrisRcvd509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>125000</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>159000</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>179892</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>200892</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>165000</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>829784</TotalAmt>
      </GiftsGrantsContrisRcvd509Grp>
      <GrossReceiptsAdmissionsGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>29175</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>24676</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>3814</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>1542</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>209</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>59416</TotalAmt>
      </GrossReceiptsAdmissionsGrp>
      <GrossReceiptsNonUnrltBusGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </GrossReceiptsNonUnrltBusGrp>
      <TaxRevLeviedOrgnztnlBnft509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </TaxRevLeviedOrgnztnlBnft509Grp>
      <GovtFurnSrvcFcltsVl509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </GovtFurnSrvcFcltsVl509Grp>
      <Total509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>154175</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>183676</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>183706</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>202434</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>165209</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>889200</TotalAmt>
      </Total509Grp>
      <AmountsRcvdDsqlfyPersonGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </AmountsRcvdDsqlfyPersonGrp>
      <SubstantialContributorsAmtGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>8810</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>5707</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>14517</TotalAmt>
      </SubstantialContributorsAmtGrp>
      <SubstAndDsqlfyPrsnsTotGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>8810</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>5707</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>14517</TotalAmt>
      </SubstAndDsqlfyPrsnsTotGrp>
      <PublicSupportTotal509Amt>874683</PublicSupportTotal509Amt>
      <GrossInvestmentIncome509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>372</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>655</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>473</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>198</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>147</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>1845</TotalAmt>
      </GrossInvestmentIncome509Grp>
      <Post1975UBTIGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </Post1975UBTIGrp>
      <InvestmentIncomeAndUBTIGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>372</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>655</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>473</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>198</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>147</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>1845</TotalAmt>
      </InvestmentIncomeAndUBTIGrp>
      <NetIncomeFromOtherUBIGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </NetIncomeFromOtherUBIGrp>
      <OtherIncome509Grp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>0</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>0</TotalAmt>
      </OtherIncome509Grp>
      <TotalSupportCalendarYearGrp>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>154547</CurrentTaxYearMinus4YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>184331</CurrentTaxYearMinus3YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>184179</CurrentTaxYearMinus2YearsAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>202632</CurrentTaxYearMinus1YearAmt>
        <CurrentTaxYearAmt>165356</CurrentTaxYearAmt>
        <TotalAmt>891045</TotalAmt>
      </TotalSupportCalendarYearGrp>
      <PublicSupportCY509Pct>0.98164</PublicSupportCY509Pct>
      <PublicSupportPY509Pct>0.9497</PublicSupportPY509Pct>
      <InvestmentIncomeCYPct>0.00207</InvestmentIncomeCYPct>
      <InvestmentIncomePYPct>0.00216</InvestmentIncomePYPct>
      <ThirtyThrPctSuprtTestsPY509Ind>X</ThirtyThrPctSuprtTestsPY509Ind>
    </IRS990ScheduleA>
    <IRS990ScheduleB documentId="R000003" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <ContributorInformationGrp>
        <ContributorNum>RESTRICTED</ContributorNum>
        <ContributorBusinessName>
          <BusinessNameLine1>RESTRICTED</BusinessNameLine1>
        </ContributorBusinessName>
        <ContributorUSAddress>
          <AddressLine1>RESTRICTED</AddressLine1>
          <AddressLine2>RESTRICTED</AddressLine2>
          <City>RESTRICTED</City>
          <State>RESTRICTED</State>
          <ZIPCode>RESTRICTED</ZIPCode>
        </ContributorUSAddress>
        <TotalContributionsAmt>RESTRICTED</TotalContributionsAmt>
      </ContributorInformationGrp>
    </IRS990ScheduleB>
    <IRS990ScheduleO documentId="R000004" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990-EZ, Part I, Line 16</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>Advertising, Entertainment and Meals, Business Insurance, Licenses and Fees, Office Supplies, Miscellaneous, Seminars/Training</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990-EZ, Part I, Line 20</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>SCEPI has a small loan fund that originated from a RD/USDA grant. In 2022, SCEPI loaned $71,040 to a business in Bonduel, WI.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
    </IRS990ScheduleO>
  </ReturnData>
</Return>