<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Return returnVersion="2022v5.0" xmlns="http://www.irs.gov/efile" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <ReturnHeader binaryAttachmentCnt="0">
    <ReturnTs>2023-03-22T16:55:10-07:00</ReturnTs>
    <TaxPeriodEndDt>2022-12-31</TaxPeriodEndDt>
    <ReturnTypeCd>990</ReturnTypeCd>
    <TaxPeriodBeginDt>2022-01-01</TaxPeriodBeginDt>
    <Filer>
      <EIN>821137996</EIN>
      <BusinessName>
        <BusinessNameLine1Txt>YPO Gold EuroChapter Inc</BusinessNameLine1Txt>
      </BusinessName>
      <BusinessNameControlTxt>YPOG</BusinessNameControlTxt>
      <PhoneNum>4129791441</PhoneNum>
      <USAddress>
        <AddressLine1Txt>431 Maple Ave</AddressLine1Txt>
        <CityNm>Pittsburgh</CityNm>
        <StateAbbreviationCd>PA</StateAbbreviationCd>
        <ZIPCd>15218</ZIPCd>
      </USAddress>
    </Filer>
    <BusinessOfficerGrp>
      <PersonNm>Mark Gitomer</PersonNm>
      <PersonTitleTxt>Treasurer</PersonTitleTxt>
      <PhoneNum>4129791441</PhoneNum>
      <SignatureDt>2023-03-31</SignatureDt>
    </BusinessOfficerGrp>
    <IRSResponsiblePrtyInfoCurrInd>1</IRSResponsiblePrtyInfoCurrInd>
    <AdditionalFilerInformation>
      <TrustedCustomerGrp>
        <TrustedCustomerCd>1</TrustedCustomerCd>
        <OOBSecurityVerificationCd>11</OOBSecurityVerificationCd>
        <LastSubmissionRqrOOBCd>0</LastSubmissionRqrOOBCd>
        <AuthenticationAssuranceLevelCd>AAL2</AuthenticationAssuranceLevelCd>
      </TrustedCustomerGrp>
    </AdditionalFilerInformation>
    <TaxYr>2022</TaxYr>
    <BuildTS>2023-04-26 12:10:37Z</BuildTS>
  </ReturnHeader>
  <ReturnData documentCnt="4">
    <IRS990 documentId="R000001" referenceDocumentId="R000004" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <PrincipalOfficerNm>Mark Gitomer</PrincipalOfficerNm>
      <USAddress>
        <AddressLine1Txt>431 Maple Ave</AddressLine1Txt>
        <CityNm>Pittsburgh</CityNm>
        <StateAbbreviationCd>PA</StateAbbreviationCd>
        <ZIPCd>15218</ZIPCd>
      </USAddress>
      <GrossReceiptsAmt>29953</GrossReceiptsAmt>
      <GroupReturnForAffiliatesInd>0</GroupReturnForAffiliatesInd>
      <GroupExemptionNum>7096</GroupExemptionNum>
      <Organization501cInd organization501cTypeTxt="6">X</Organization501cInd>
      <WebsiteAddressTxt>www.ypo.org</WebsiteAddressTxt>
      <TypeOfOrganizationCorpInd>X</TypeOfOrganizationCorpInd>
      <FormationYr>2017</FormationYr>
      <LegalDomicileStateCd>PA</LegalDomicileStateCd>
      <ActivityOrMissionDesc>To provide an association for international executives who have mutual interests. To develop, promote, and exchange experiences, ideas, and business practices for the purpose of improving executive performance, assisting community development and services.</ActivityOrMissionDesc>
      <VotingMembersGoverningBodyCnt>7</VotingMembersGoverningBodyCnt>
      <VotingMembersIndependentCnt>7</VotingMembersIndependentCnt>
      <TotalEmployeeCnt>0</TotalEmployeeCnt>
      <TotalVolunteersCnt>6</TotalVolunteersCnt>
      <TotalGrossUBIAmt>0</TotalGrossUBIAmt>
      <NetUnrelatedBusTxblIncmAmt>0</NetUnrelatedBusTxblIncmAmt>
      <PYContributionsGrantsAmt>0</PYContributionsGrantsAmt>
      <CYContributionsGrantsAmt>0</CYContributionsGrantsAmt>
      <PYProgramServiceRevenueAmt>131962</PYProgramServiceRevenueAmt>
      <CYProgramServiceRevenueAmt>29953</CYProgramServiceRevenueAmt>
      <PYInvestmentIncomeAmt>0</PYInvestmentIncomeAmt>
      <CYInvestmentIncomeAmt>0</CYInvestmentIncomeAmt>
      <PYOtherRevenueAmt>0</PYOtherRevenueAmt>
      <CYOtherRevenueAmt>0</CYOtherRevenueAmt>
      <PYTotalRevenueAmt>131962</PYTotalRevenueAmt>
      <CYTotalRevenueAmt>29953</CYTotalRevenueAmt>
      <PYGrantsAndSimilarPaidAmt>0</PYGrantsAndSimilarPaidAmt>
      <CYGrantsAndSimilarPaidAmt>0</CYGrantsAndSimilarPaidAmt>
      <PYBenefitsPaidToMembersAmt>0</PYBenefitsPaidToMembersAmt>
      <CYBenefitsPaidToMembersAmt>0</CYBenefitsPaidToMembersAmt>
      <PYSalariesCompEmpBnftPaidAmt>0</PYSalariesCompEmpBnftPaidAmt>
      <CYSalariesCompEmpBnftPaidAmt>0</CYSalariesCompEmpBnftPaidAmt>
      <PYTotalProfFndrsngExpnsAmt>0</PYTotalProfFndrsngExpnsAmt>
      <CYTotalProfFndrsngExpnsAmt>0</CYTotalProfFndrsngExpnsAmt>
      <CYTotalFundraisingExpenseAmt>0</CYTotalFundraisingExpenseAmt>
      <PYOtherExpensesAmt>147779</PYOtherExpensesAmt>
      <CYOtherExpensesAmt>-31332</CYOtherExpensesAmt>
      <PYTotalExpensesAmt>147779</PYTotalExpensesAmt>
      <CYTotalExpensesAmt>-31332</CYTotalExpensesAmt>
      <PYRevenuesLessExpensesAmt>-15817</PYRevenuesLessExpensesAmt>
      <CYRevenuesLessExpensesAmt>61285</CYRevenuesLessExpensesAmt>
      <TotalAssetsBOYAmt>648480</TotalAssetsBOYAmt>
      <TotalAssetsEOYAmt>335145</TotalAssetsEOYAmt>
      <TotalLiabilitiesBOYAmt>543288</TotalLiabilitiesBOYAmt>
      <TotalLiabilitiesEOYAmt>168668</TotalLiabilitiesEOYAmt>
      <NetAssetsOrFundBalancesBOYAmt>105192</NetAssetsOrFundBalancesBOYAmt>
      <NetAssetsOrFundBalancesEOYAmt>166477</NetAssetsOrFundBalancesEOYAmt>
      <MissionDesc>To provide an association for international executives who have mutual interests. To develop, promote, and exchange experiences, ideas, and business practices for the purpose of improving executive performance. To develop more efficient and effective business practices for the benefit of customers, employees, shareholders, communities, and the industries served. To visit and engage with community leaders around the world to discuss issues and problems. To gain understanding of local characteristics and offer ideas and solutions from experiences of business and community leaders in the more than 20 countries represented. To assist in economic development of areas visited by meeting locals and sharing ideas.</MissionDesc>
      <SignificantNewProgramSrvcInd>0</SignificantNewProgramSrvcInd>
      <SignificantChangeInd>0</SignificantChangeInd>
      <ExpenseAmt>134940</ExpenseAmt>
      <GrantAmt>0</GrantAmt>
      <RevenueAmt>-12581</RevenueAmt>
      <Desc>2022 marked the first year since covid that in-person program services could occur. Our first event was in Amsterdam and The Hague from 19 to 24 May. Our hosts focused the education on three tracks, water management in the face of climate change, legalized prostitution and sex trafficking, and issues with essentially legalized soft drugs. The permissiveness of the Netherlands was on full display. The first event was the Global Investment Forum. Interestingly, very few participants had changed much of their investment strategy during covid. Real assets were preferred by those who could access and understand them, while crypto currencies were not a factor at all. Most relied upon the usual financial assets, stocks and bonds. The next session included a city walk to the Red Light District where the themes were Prostitution and the Trading of Women and Amsterdam's Policy on Soft Drugs. The moderator was Rob Van Hulst, an entertainer who hosted a TV show in the 90's about the Red Light District. After doing that, Rob became an advocate for the predominantly female sex workers. He now travels throughout the Netherlands making high school presentations about sex trafficking. Many of our attendees found this to be a very worthwhile endeavor and planned to investigate doing the same in their many home countries. Also presenting was Ron Beekmeijer, a policeman. Ron, in his capacity as a policeman, worked on the legalization of prostitution after working for several years policing the Red Light District. His explanation of the reasons for the legalization boiled down to protection of the women and efforts to minimize transmission of sexual diseases. Lastly, Simone Van Breda presented the case for soft drug legalization in her capacity as the Chairwoman of the Dutch Association of Cannabis Retailers. The next day was focused on water management and climate change. The moderator was Jules Kortenhorst, CEO of the Rocky Mountain Institute, a forward looking think tank. The participants included Rogier Van Der Sande, the Chairman of the Union of Water Boards and Bart Van Den Hurk, a co-author of the IPCC report on weather and climate. Also presenting was Bas Jonkman, a professor of hydraulic engineering at Delft University and Geert Van De Wouw, the managing director of Shell Ventures. The differing perspectives were quite interesting and the Netherlands, with much of their land already below sea level, had obvious concerns about what might happen. Finally, on the last day, Jaap De Hoop Scheffer, the former Secretary General of NATO and the former Dutch Minister of Foreign Affairs spent several hours with our group. A true Dutchman, he arrived and departed on his bicycle with a conspicuous absence of any security despite his NATO and sovereign status. His stories about historical NATO issues were extremely illustrative of the difficulties that the primary national and regional defense group has had and how they were or were not overcome. Since the event was priced pre-covid the ensuing inflation made the event operate at a loss to the EuroChapter. Since all of the revenue and some of the expenses occurred several years ago, the below numbers are only 2022's activity. Actual total revenue was $138,118 and expense was $144,535 for a $6,417 loss. 2022 revenue is negative because of member attendance cancellations.</Desc>
      <ProgSrvcAccomActy2Grp>
        <ExpenseAmt>142273</ExpenseAmt>
        <GrantAmt>0</GrantAmt>
        <RevenueAmt>-3860</RevenueAmt>
        <Desc>The year's second event was held in Lisbon and Porto, Portugal from 8 to 13 September. The Global Investment Forum was interesting because of the large number of attendees who were making or considering Portuguese real estate investments. It seems that with a real estate investment above a certain level, Portuguese citizenship can be obtained after a few year's wait. This is attractive to some of the attendees for whom an EU passport would be a great convenience. Crypto's diminished value attracted some discussion but it was once again mainly status quo. Portugal has excellent universities and graduate schools. This has spawned more than its share of high tech companies. First on our agenda was a session with the founders and operators of Unbabel, an artificial intelligence powered human language translation platform. Vasco Pedro, the co-founder and CEO described his operations in Lisbon and San Francisco. The company has raised $91mm from the venture capital market. Unbabel is the first Portuguese company to be accepted into the Y Combinator accelerator program, a significant achievement. After describing the innovation ecosystem in Portugal, the host company detailed its experience in starting, hiring staff, marketing, and operating from start up to a relatively mature company status. The energy of the locals was obvious as were their abilities. The next speaker was Miguel Assis, a more typical entrepreneur in the incentive travel and events business. Miguel founded Voquin and continues to be quite innovative within his sector. The third speaker was Jordi Vilanova, the vice president of Mercan Group. Jordi is developing real estate projects in Portugal somewhat predicated on immigration for investment in the tourism sector. Interestingly, his firm has offices in the US, Canada, the Emirates, China, and India. The next day was a deep dive into the educational ecosystem at the NOVA School of Business and Economics. Various professors, students, and graduates addressed the group, demonstrating the success of the school, and explaining the talent creation that was seen the previous day. The ifrst speaker was Professor Paula Marques, the executive director for business transformation at NOVA. With a background from Mercer and PWC Consulting, Paula focuses on ways to prepare humans to work along side of machines , both robotic and artificial intelligence. Professor Alisson Avila, NOVA's head of applied strategy was next. He discussed his research and efforts to apply anthropology to business and innovation strategy. He also contributes much of his personal time to trying to enhance transparency to fight corruption in public management. Pedro Brita, NOVA's dean of executive education described how the school's program brings in executives to train them how to align human resources with business competitiveness and growth. Moving on to Porto, the group met with Paulo Portas, also a professor and politician. He was the leader of the CDS-Peoples Party from 1998 to and 2005 and then again from 2007 to 2016. He has served as Portugal's deputy prime minister, minister of state and foreign affairs, and minister of defence. His time in various offices coincided with Portugal's rise in Europe. Porto had been designated as a European City of the Year and as such had attracted public infrastructure investment which in turn had seeded far greater private investment. The city was literally transformed and tourism has boomed. And, of course, while in Porto, the group was treated to a presentation by Graham's of the port wine industry for which the city is renowned. Again, since the revenues for this event had been mostly collected before covid, the below numbers reflect only the activity which occurred in 2022. Actual total revenue was $162,095 and expenses were $153,8334 for a net of $8,761. This was offset by Amsterdam's deficit yielding a virtual breakeven for the year as is the Chapter's intent. Again, the negative revenue is due to members' cancellations during 2022.</Desc>
      </ProgSrvcAccomActy2Grp>
      <ProgSrvcAccomActy3Grp>
        <ExpenseAmt>0</ExpenseAmt>
        <GrantAmt>0</GrantAmt>
        <RevenueAmt>9274</RevenueAmt>
        <Desc>There was some financial activity for the event to be held in Stockholm in 2023. It is detailed below.</Desc>
      </ProgSrvcAccomActy3Grp>
      <TotalOtherProgSrvcExpenseAmt>0</TotalOtherProgSrvcExpenseAmt>
      <TotalOtherProgSrvcGrantAmt>0</TotalOtherProgSrvcGrantAmt>
      <TotalOtherProgSrvcRevenueAmt>0</TotalOtherProgSrvcRevenueAmt>
      <TotalProgramServiceExpensesAmt>277213</TotalProgramServiceExpensesAmt>
      <DescribedInSection501c3Ind>0</DescribedInSection501c3Ind>
      <ScheduleBRequiredInd>0</ScheduleBRequiredInd>
      <PoliticalCampaignActyInd>0</PoliticalCampaignActyInd>
      <SubjectToProxyTaxInd referenceDocumentId="R000002">1</SubjectToProxyTaxInd>
      <DonorAdvisedFundInd>0</DonorAdvisedFundInd>
      <ConservationEasementsInd>0</ConservationEasementsInd>
      <CollectionsOfArtInd>0</CollectionsOfArtInd>
      <CreditCounselingInd>0</CreditCounselingInd>
      <DonorRstrOrQuasiEndowmentsInd>0</DonorRstrOrQuasiEndowmentsInd>
      <ReportLandBuildingEquipmentInd>0</ReportLandBuildingEquipmentInd>
      <ReportInvestmentsOtherSecInd>0</ReportInvestmentsOtherSecInd>
      <ReportProgramRelatedInvstInd>0</ReportProgramRelatedInvstInd>
      <ReportOtherAssetsInd>0</ReportOtherAssetsInd>
      <ReportOtherLiabilitiesInd>0</ReportOtherLiabilitiesInd>
      <IncludeFIN48FootnoteInd>0</IncludeFIN48FootnoteInd>
      <IndependentAuditFinclStmtInd>0</IndependentAuditFinclStmtInd>
      <ConsolidatedAuditFinclStmtInd>0</ConsolidatedAuditFinclStmtInd>
      <SchoolOperatingInd>0</SchoolOperatingInd>
      <ForeignOfficeInd>0</ForeignOfficeInd>
      <ForeignActivitiesInd referenceDocumentId="R000003">1</ForeignActivitiesInd>
      <MoreThan5000KToOrgInd>0</MoreThan5000KToOrgInd>
      <MoreThan5000KToIndividualsInd>0</MoreThan5000KToIndividualsInd>
      <ProfessionalFundraisingInd>0</ProfessionalFundraisingInd>
      <FundraisingActivitiesInd>0</FundraisingActivitiesInd>
      <GamingActivitiesInd>0</GamingActivitiesInd>
      <OperateHospitalInd>0</OperateHospitalInd>
      <GrantsToOrganizationsInd>0</GrantsToOrganizationsInd>
      <GrantsToIndividualsInd>0</GrantsToIndividualsInd>
      <ScheduleJRequiredInd>0</ScheduleJRequiredInd>
      <TaxExemptBondsInd>0</TaxExemptBondsInd>
      <LoanOutstandingInd>0</LoanOutstandingInd>
      <GrantToRelatedPersonInd>0</GrantToRelatedPersonInd>
      <BusinessRlnWithOrgMemInd>0</BusinessRlnWithOrgMemInd>
      <BusinessRlnWithFamMemInd>0</BusinessRlnWithFamMemInd>
      <BusinessRlnWith35CtrlEntInd>0</BusinessRlnWith35CtrlEntInd>
      <DeductibleNonCashContriInd>0</DeductibleNonCashContriInd>
      <DeductibleArtContributionInd>0</DeductibleArtContributionInd>
      <TerminateOperationsInd>0</TerminateOperationsInd>
      <PartialLiquidationInd>0</PartialLiquidationInd>
      <DisregardedEntityInd>0</DisregardedEntityInd>
      <RelatedEntityInd>0</RelatedEntityInd>
      <RelatedOrganizationCtrlEntInd>0</RelatedOrganizationCtrlEntInd>
      <ActivitiesConductedPrtshpInd>0</ActivitiesConductedPrtshpInd>
      <ScheduleORequiredInd>1</ScheduleORequiredInd>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartVInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartVInd>
      <IRPDocumentCnt>0</IRPDocumentCnt>
      <IRPDocumentW2GCnt>0</IRPDocumentW2GCnt>
      <EmployeeCnt>0</EmployeeCnt>
      <UnrelatedBusIncmOverLimitInd>0</UnrelatedBusIncmOverLimitInd>
      <ForeignFinancialAccountInd>1</ForeignFinancialAccountInd>
      <ForeignCountryCd>BE</ForeignCountryCd>
      <ProhibitedTaxShelterTransInd>0</ProhibitedTaxShelterTransInd>
      <TaxablePartyNotificationInd>0</TaxablePartyNotificationInd>
      <NondeductibleContributionsInd>0</NondeductibleContributionsInd>
      <IndoorTanningServicesInd>0</IndoorTanningServicesInd>
      <SubjToTaxRmnrtnExPrchtPymtInd>0</SubjToTaxRmnrtnExPrchtPymtInd>
      <SubjectToExcsTaxNetInvstIncInd>0</SubjectToExcsTaxNetInvstIncInd>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartVIInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartVIInd>
      <GoverningBodyVotingMembersCnt>7</GoverningBodyVotingMembersCnt>
      <IndependentVotingMemberCnt>7</IndependentVotingMemberCnt>
      <FamilyOrBusinessRlnInd>0</FamilyOrBusinessRlnInd>
      <DelegationOfMgmtDutiesInd>0</DelegationOfMgmtDutiesInd>
      <ChangeToOrgDocumentsInd>0</ChangeToOrgDocumentsInd>
      <MaterialDiversionOrMisuseInd>0</MaterialDiversionOrMisuseInd>
      <MembersOrStockholdersInd>0</MembersOrStockholdersInd>
      <ElectionOfBoardMembersInd>0</ElectionOfBoardMembersInd>
      <DecisionsSubjectToApprovaInd>0</DecisionsSubjectToApprovaInd>
      <MinutesOfGoverningBodyInd>1</MinutesOfGoverningBodyInd>
      <MinutesOfCommitteesInd>0</MinutesOfCommitteesInd>
      <OfficerMailingAddressInd>0</OfficerMailingAddressInd>
      <LocalChaptersInd>0</LocalChaptersInd>
      <Form990ProvidedToGvrnBodyInd>1</Form990ProvidedToGvrnBodyInd>
      <ConflictOfInterestPolicyInd>1</ConflictOfInterestPolicyInd>
      <AnnualDisclosureCoveredPrsnInd>1</AnnualDisclosureCoveredPrsnInd>
      <RegularMonitoringEnfrcInd>1</RegularMonitoringEnfrcInd>
      <WhistleblowerPolicyInd>0</WhistleblowerPolicyInd>
      <DocumentRetentionPolicyInd>1</DocumentRetentionPolicyInd>
      <CompensationProcessCEOInd>0</CompensationProcessCEOInd>
      <CompensationProcessOtherInd>0</CompensationProcessOtherInd>
      <InvestmentInJointVentureInd>0</InvestmentInJointVentureInd>
      <UponRequestInd>X</UponRequestInd>
      <BooksInCareOfDetail>
        <PersonNm>Mark Gitomer</PersonNm>
        <PhoneNum>4129791441</PhoneNum>
        <USAddress>
          <AddressLine1Txt>431 Maple Ave</AddressLine1Txt>
          <CityNm>Pittsburgh</CityNm>
          <StateAbbreviationCd>PA</StateAbbreviationCd>
          <ZIPCd>15218</ZIPCd>
        </USAddress>
      </BooksInCareOfDetail>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Erik Sellberg</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Membership Chairperson</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>1</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Willem Kok</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Chapter Chairperson</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>3</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Mike Saltman</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Education Chairperson</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>1</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Giles Clarke</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Assistant Education Chair</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>3</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Tore Steen</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>2nd Assistant Education Chairperson</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>1</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Michael Chesser</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Forum Chair</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>1</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
        <PersonNm>Mark Gitomer</PersonNm>
        <TitleTxt>Treasurer</TitleTxt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRt>3</AverageHoursPerWeekRt>
        <AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>0</AverageHoursPerWeekRltdOrgRt>
        <IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>X</IndividualTrusteeOrDirectorInd>
        <ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
        <ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>0</ReportableCompFromRltdOrgAmt>
        <OtherCompensationAmt>0</OtherCompensationAmt>
      </Form990PartVIISectionAGrp>
      <TotalReportableCompFromOrgAmt>0</TotalReportableCompFromOrgAmt>
      <TotReportableCompRltdOrgAmt>0</TotReportableCompRltdOrgAmt>
      <TotalOtherCompensationAmt>0</TotalOtherCompensationAmt>
      <IndivRcvdGreaterThan100KCnt>0</IndivRcvdGreaterThan100KCnt>
      <FormerOfcrEmployeesListedInd>0</FormerOfcrEmployeesListedInd>
      <TotalCompGreaterThan150KInd>0</TotalCompGreaterThan150KInd>
      <CompensationFromOtherSrcsInd>0</CompensationFromOtherSrcsInd>
      <CntrctRcvdGreaterThan100KCnt>0</CntrctRcvdGreaterThan100KCnt>
      <TotalContributionsAmt>0</TotalContributionsAmt>
      <ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
        <Desc>Program Service Fees</Desc>
        <BusinessCd>900099</BusinessCd>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>37120</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>37120</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
      <ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
        <Desc>Amsterdam Program Fees</Desc>
        <BusinessCd>900099</BusinessCd>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>-12581</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>-12581</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
      <ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
        <Desc>Portugal Program Fees</Desc>
        <BusinessCd>900099</BusinessCd>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>-3860</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>-3860</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
      <ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
        <Desc>Stockholm Program Fees</Desc>
        <BusinessCd>900099</BusinessCd>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>9274</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>9274</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </ProgramServiceRevenueGrp>
      <TotalOthProgramServiceRevGrp>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>0</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>0</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </TotalOthProgramServiceRevGrp>
      <TotalProgramServiceRevenueAmt>29953</TotalProgramServiceRevenueAmt>
      <RentalIncomeOrLossGrp>
        <RealAmt>0</RealAmt>
        <PersonalAmt>0</PersonalAmt>
      </RentalIncomeOrLossGrp>
      <GainOrLossGrp>
        <SecuritiesAmt>0</SecuritiesAmt>
        <OtherAmt>0</OtherAmt>
      </GainOrLossGrp>
      <OtherRevenueTotalAmt>0</OtherRevenueTotalAmt>
      <TotalRevenueGrp>
        <TotalRevenueColumnAmt>29953</TotalRevenueColumnAmt>
        <RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>29953</RelatedOrExemptFuncIncomeAmt>
        <UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>0</UnrelatedBusinessRevenueAmt>
        <ExclusionAmt>0</ExclusionAmt>
      </TotalRevenueGrp>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartIXInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartIXInd>
      <FeesForServicesManagementGrp>
        <TotalAmt>40262</TotalAmt>
      </FeesForServicesManagementGrp>
      <OfficeExpensesGrp>
        <TotalAmt>3302</TotalAmt>
      </OfficeExpensesGrp>
      <OtherExpensesGrp>
        <Desc>Amsterdam Expenses</Desc>
        <TotalAmt>134940</TotalAmt>
      </OtherExpensesGrp>
      <OtherExpensesGrp>
        <Desc>Portugal Expenses</Desc>
        <TotalAmt>142273</TotalAmt>
      </OtherExpensesGrp>
      <OtherExpensesGrp>
        <Desc>Deferred Program Expense</Desc>
        <TotalAmt>-314625</TotalAmt>
      </OtherExpensesGrp>
      <OtherExpensesGrp>
        <Desc>Dollar Euro Exchange Rate Change</Desc>
        <TotalAmt>-37484</TotalAmt>
      </OtherExpensesGrp>
      <TotalFunctionalExpensesGrp>
        <TotalAmt>-31332</TotalAmt>
        <ProgramServicesAmt>0</ProgramServicesAmt>
        <ManagementAndGeneralAmt>0</ManagementAndGeneralAmt>
        <FundraisingAmt>0</FundraisingAmt>
      </TotalFunctionalExpensesGrp>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartXInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartXInd>
      <CashNonInterestBearingGrp>
        <BOYAmt>613595</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>332006</EOYAmt>
      </CashNonInterestBearingGrp>
      <AccountsReceivableGrp>
        <BOYAmt>34885</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>3139</EOYAmt>
      </AccountsReceivableGrp>
      <TotalAssetsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>648480</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>335145</EOYAmt>
      </TotalAssetsGrp>
      <DeferredRevenueGrp>
        <BOYAmt>543288</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>168668</EOYAmt>
      </DeferredRevenueGrp>
      <TotalLiabilitiesGrp>
        <BOYAmt>543288</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>168668</EOYAmt>
      </TotalLiabilitiesGrp>
      <OrganizationFollowsFASB117Ind>X</OrganizationFollowsFASB117Ind>
      <NoDonorRestrictionNetAssetsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>105192</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>166477</EOYAmt>
      </NoDonorRestrictionNetAssetsGrp>
      <DonorRestrictionNetAssetsGrp>
        <BOYAmt>0</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>0</EOYAmt>
      </DonorRestrictionNetAssetsGrp>
      <TotalNetAssetsFundBalanceGrp>
        <BOYAmt>105192</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>166477</EOYAmt>
      </TotalNetAssetsFundBalanceGrp>
      <TotLiabNetAssetsFundBalanceGrp>
        <BOYAmt>648480</BOYAmt>
        <EOYAmt>335145</EOYAmt>
      </TotLiabNetAssetsFundBalanceGrp>
      <InfoInScheduleOPartXIInd>X</InfoInScheduleOPartXIInd>
      <ReconcilationRevenueExpnssAmt>61285</ReconcilationRevenueExpnssAmt>
      <NetUnrlzdGainsLossesInvstAmt>0</NetUnrlzdGainsLossesInvstAmt>
      <DonatedServicesAndUseFcltsAmt>0</DonatedServicesAndUseFcltsAmt>
      <InvestmentExpenseAmt>0</InvestmentExpenseAmt>
      <PriorPeriodAdjustmentsAmt>0</PriorPeriodAdjustmentsAmt>
      <OtherChangesInNetAssetsAmt>0</OtherChangesInNetAssetsAmt>
      <MethodOfAccountingAccrualInd>X</MethodOfAccountingAccrualInd>
      <AccountantCompileOrReviewInd>0</AccountantCompileOrReviewInd>
      <FSAuditedInd>0</FSAuditedInd>
      <FederalGrantAuditRequiredInd>0</FederalGrantAuditRequiredInd>
    </IRS990>
    <IRS990ScheduleC documentId="R000002" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <SubstantiallyAllDuesNondedInd>0</SubstantiallyAllDuesNondedInd>
      <OnlyInHouseLobbyingInd>1</OnlyInHouseLobbyingInd>
      <AgreeCarryoverPriorYearInd>0</AgreeCarryoverPriorYearInd>
    </IRS990ScheduleC>
    <IRS990ScheduleF documentId="R000003" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <AccountActivitiesOutsideUSGrp>
        <RegionTxt>Europe (including Iceland and Greenland)</RegionTxt>
        <OfficesCnt>0</OfficesCnt>
        <EmployeeCnt>0</EmployeeCnt>
        <TypeOfActivitiesConductedTxt>Program Services</TypeOfActivitiesConductedTxt>
        <SpecificServicesProvidedTxt>The Chapter is comprised of mostly European members. Most program service events are held in Europe. There are no employees of the Chapter other than independent contractors and local agencies used to assist with events. The below 2022 expenditures were for the program service events in Amsterdam (134,940) and Lisbon ($142,273).</SpecificServicesProvidedTxt>
        <RegionTotalExpendituresAmt>277213</RegionTotalExpendituresAmt>
      </AccountActivitiesOutsideUSGrp>
      <TotalOfficeCnt>0</TotalOfficeCnt>
      <TotalEmployeeCnt>0</TotalEmployeeCnt>
      <TotalSpentAmt>277213</TotalSpentAmt>
      <TransferToForeignCorpInd>0</TransferToForeignCorpInd>
      <InterestInForeignTrustInd>0</InterestInForeignTrustInd>
      <ForeignCorpOwnershipInd>0</ForeignCorpOwnershipInd>
      <PassiveForeignInvestmestCoInd>0</PassiveForeignInvestmestCoInd>
      <ForeignPartnershipInd>0</ForeignPartnershipInd>
      <BoycottCountriesInd>0</BoycottCountriesInd>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Schedule F, Part I, Line 3</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>Member Networking and Program Service Events were held in Amsterdam, Netherlands and Lisbon, Portugal.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
    </IRS990ScheduleF>
    <IRS990ScheduleO documentId="R000004" softwareId="22015720" softwareVersionNum="v1.00">
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Header, Line A</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>The YPO Gold Euro Chapter is a separate corporation from the Young President's Organization Inc. (12-1770417) but is included in its 501c6 blanket exemption number 7096. In April 2017, the Chapter was incorporated in Pennsylvania after having previously been domiciled in Sweden. Most of the Chapter members are European and most of the Chapter events are held in Europe. The Chapter accounts are denominated in euros and euro funds are held at the Wise Europe SA Bank in Brussels, Belgium. The US dollar account is held at PNC Bank NA in Pittsburgh.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part V, Line 4a</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>Since most of the Chapter members and events are in Europe, a euro account is maintained with Wise, an internet wire transfer platform with its associated commercial bank located in Belgium.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part VI, Section A, Line 8b</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>There are no committees with authority to act on behalf of the governing body. All decisions are made and directed by the Board. Minutes of each Board meeting are written up and distributed to the Board and any other interested member.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part VI, Section B, Line 11b</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>A draft of Form 990 and required schedules is prepared and reviewed by the Treasurer of the Chapter. Upon completion of this review, a complete copy of Form 990 and related Schedules is provided to each member of the Board in advance of filing with the Internal Revenue Service.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part VI, Section B, Line 12c</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>At the end of every fiscal (calendar) year, when the new Board is constituted, a questionnaire is provided to each Board member which must be completed to identify any conflicts with the organization. If a conflict is noted, the individual Board member shall not vote or use his / her personal influence on the matter which gives rise to the conflict.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part VI, Section C, Line 19</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>The Chapter makes its governance documents, financial statements, and conflict of interest policy available to the public upon request. It is also available on the Internal Revenue website.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part IX, Line 11a</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>A part time Chapter administrator, living in Berlin, Germany, provides services to the Chapter. Due to a maternity leave, an additional part time administrator, living in Amsterdam, Netherlands is a temporary replacement.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part IX, Line 24a - 24d</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>Since the Chapter invoices event participants approximately one year in advance, the fees collected are not recorded as income but rather are recognized as deferred revenue. A corresponding deferred program expense is recorded. Event delays related to covid, pushed that out to two to three years in advance since events were postponed. Depending upon the balance at the end of the year, this amount is adjusted to actual at the end of the fiscal year and offset by any prepaid future program expenses. This amount had become larger than normal due to the event postponed by covid travel restrictions. There had been prepaid fees for three events including the two events held in 2022 and a third to be held in 2023. Members are permitted to cancel attendance and request fee refunds prior to the events, sometimes creating negative program fee amounts within a fiscal year.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part X, Line 19</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>Deferred revenue is generated when Event Fees and Program Service Fees are collected in years prior to the event or activity. It is customary for the Chapter to invoice attending members 12 to 15 months prior to each event.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
      <SupplementalInformationDetail>
        <FormAndLineReferenceDesc>Form 990, Part XI, Line 9</FormAndLineReferenceDesc>
        <ExplanationTxt>All Chapter accounting is in euros. Changes in the IRS published exchange rates can create book gains and losses. With the relative strength of the dollar relative to the euro in 2022, the Chapter enjoyed a large gain since most funds are held in US dollars at PNC Bank NA. and nearly all expenses are denominated in euros. Some of this gain has already been reversed in the 1st quarter of 2023.</ExplanationTxt>
      </SupplementalInformationDetail>
    </IRS990ScheduleO>
  </ReturnData>
</Return>